Contact

92993081676 (Mobile) felipebrunner@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/felipe brunner-21095018a (LinkedIn)

Main competencies

Social media

Video edition

Marketing

Felipe Brunner

Head of the Civil Defense and Advisory Division

Parintins, Amazonas, Brazil

Summary

My work in the editing business started in 2008 with the well-known program Sony Vegas, since then I have been learning and progressing in audio visual.

In 2009 I started photographing and advising political candidates and in 2010 I joined the Faculty of Journalism where I developed projects, worked harder on learning photography and media.

In 2013 I was invited to participate in the Amazon Film Festival, where I observed how the festival and cinema behave.

In 2013 I made my first documentary in a community called Caranã where a typical fruit from this region, the bacaba, took place.

In 2014 I competed with a video in a contest where

I won first place, winning an iphone, ipad and ipod. Then I applied for a program called sala de cinema that edited and helped in the production, this being a college project.

I competed with Sala de Cinema in the vignette category, taking first place.

In 2015 I competed with a documentary about breast cancer and I won at the regional level for best documentary, and until now I have done photography and video filming work...

Experience

Civil Defense Counselor Lafaiete

Boss

January 2018 - Present (4 years 10 months)

Cefe of the Civil Defense Administrative and Advisory Division

Candidate for Mayor

Consultancy and Production
October 2016 - Present (6 years 1 month)

Amazon, Brazil

Advice and production of the media content of referrals' candidacy cadidatos

Candidate for Councilor
Press Officer March

2012 - Present (10 years 8 months)

Amazon, Brazil

Photographer, video editor, content production.

Academic education

Federal University of Amazonas

Bachelor of Social Communication Journalism, Marketing · (2010 - 2014)